darrelconceptsghana.com 2011-11-04

# Privacy Policy- Darrel Technologies Ghana- www.darrelconceptsghana.com

Our commitment to your privacy 

* * *

**At Darrel Technologies your privacy is important to us.  
We therefor adopt effective measures to ensure the privacy of all visitors to our [website](http://www.darrelconceptsghana.com/). The following represents the policy governing collection and use of information on this site. A link to this page is available on all pages on our site.**

What Information We Collect 

We may request personal information when you place an order, request a service, answer a survey, correspond with us or engage in certain other activities on our Web site. The type of personal information we collect on this site include;

> Name   
>  Email Address   
>  Phone Number  
>  Postal Address  
> 

We may also record IP addresses of online users. IP addresses are used in trends analysis, site administration, user movement tracking, and also to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not in anyway linked to personally identifiable information. 

How we use this Information

**We use information provided to process customer orders. We will also use the email addresses provided by customers to respond to enquiries and provide support, as well as reply to emails we receive. Most Email addresses are used to provide a free subscription to our free News Letter. Such addresses are never shared with third parties.**

We use non-identifying information to improve our [website](http://www.darrelconceptsghana.com/), in order to increase its marketability and meet industry standards and changng trends. 

If at any point we would use personally identifiable information in anyway other than those stated, we will always give users a way to opt-out, or otherwise prohibit the use of such information. 

External Links 

Our website currently displays a number of links to companies with whom we have a relationship. Darrel Technologies is not responsible for the privacy practices of our business partners. We encourage you to read their privacy statements, as they may differ from ours.

**Feel free to contact the[support team](http://www.darrelconceptsghana.com/support "Customer Support") if you require additional information about our privacy policy.**

## Darrel Technologies Ltd,

Plot BA 137, High Street,   
Bantama, Kumasi, Ghana   
**+233 32 20 44387  
+233 32 20 42958   
+233 24 4528251**  

### 

* * *

Darrel Technologies Ltd. delivers "complete" web, technology, and E-business solutions that provide a back-bone (in this new age) for corporate growth and development.
